PERSONAL DATA

Name Natalie Acevedo

Phone (+351) 910-708-284

Website natalieacevedo.com

E-mail natalieacevedo25@gmail.com

Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/natalie-acevedo-plata/

GitHub https://github.com/natalieacevedo

AT A GLANCE

Quick learner software developer with a passion for coding. I have hands-on experience with React and ExpressJS-based projects. Completed 700+ hours of programming bootcamp, as well as 300+ hours of the JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures certification from FreeCodeCamp; having also solved numerous programming challenges in sites such as Codewars and Edabit.

SKILLS

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, MySQL, React, ExpressJS, Git, Bootstrap, Linux.

PROJECTS

What's on your Fridge, 2021

- React JS app that gets recipes matching a list of ingredients.
- Project management with Trello and GitHub.
- See it at: https://natalieacevedo.github.io/what-s-in-your-fridge/#

Personality App, 2022

- React JS app.
- See it at: https://natalieacevedo.github.io/personalityTest/

EDUCATION

Web Development, 700+ hours.

Wild Code School, Lisbon, Portugal.

2006-2012 Bachelor's degree, Anthropology, 4-year degree.

San Francisco State University, San Francisco, CA.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dec 2021 – Feb 2022 KinderBday (Full-stack Web Developer), Remote.

> Developed both the front-end and back-end for a start-up as part of a team of five developers. Using React and ExpressJS, following MVC best practices with a MySQL

database.

2015 - 2016Women's Building (Programs Coordinator), San Francisco, CA.

I planned and implemented employee benefit programs in order to increase staff

satisfaction. I monitored legal compliance such as labor laws.

2012 - 2015Omni Hotel (Sales Coordinator), San Francisco, CA.

> I promoted the brand in order to sell all sort of events (corporate, weddings, etc); maintained a database of accounts; participated in sales initiatives in order to meet

potential new clients.

I mentored several sales coordinators and received very positive comments from my mentees and managers alike. Was awarded employee of the trimester for my outstanding

performance and positive comments from our guests.

Spanish: native English: fluent

Languages